<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Executive Tours</title>
    <link>http://example.org/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Executive Tours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Battle of The Forts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/battle-of-the-forts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/battle-of-the-forts/</guid>
      <description>Breathe in Grenada’s rich history as you stroll through these antique stone fortifications, which hosts astonishing bird’s eye views of the Harbour, the town of St. George, Grand Anse Beach, Point Saline, and so much more.
Boast of your visit to Fort George, Grenada’s oldest fort which sits mighty at the hill top, 2 minutes outside the main city. Enjoy a striking 360 view from Fort Frederick, which showcases picture perfect ocean views, and magnificent mountainous ranges, clothed with lush vegetation and local homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Rush</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/beach-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/beach-rush/</guid>
      <description>Get-A- Way for the day as we escape to some of Grenada’s most exotic beaches. Imagine the cool Caribbean Sea breeze hugging your face, while the fine refreshing sand kisses your feet.
Hop on and hop off at four of Grenada’s must-see beach attractions. Black Bay Beach hosts attractive black sand which hugs the surrounding coastline area. If you are lucky, you just might be right on time to witness the main event over at Levera Beach, home to the Leather Back Turtles which seasonally stops by to lay their eggs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Tour</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/city-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/city-tour/</guid>
      <description>A holistic experience welcoming you with open arms to embark on a journey through the unique city of St. George’s. Enjoy majestic panoramic views of the horse-shoe-shaped harbor, the pristine Grand Anse Beach, and so much more, as Fort George awards you the opportunity to capture post card worthy pictures from Grenada’s oldest Fort, formerly known as Fort Royal. For our lovers of chocolate, we’ve got a treat for your taste buds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cocoa Sensation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/cocoa-sensation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/cocoa-sensation/</guid>
      <description>Savour the dark and healthy, pure pleasures of Grenada’s luxury organic cocoa products, as we escape to the estates and factories to witness the production process. Get the opportunity to see the cocoa in its natural habitat, break a pod and enjoy the delicious fruit while in the beautiful tropics.
At the Belmont estate you can stroll through the plantation grounds which also hosts an eatery, museum, and cocoa making facilities where they produce their own chocolate, cocoa powder, cocoa balls, and cocoa butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Executive Luxury Transfers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/executive-luxury-transfers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/executive-luxury-transfers/</guid>
      <description>No need to burden yourself with the worries of the hustle and bustle of getting from point ‘A’ to point ‘B’. We are here to ensure you have the VIP Luxury transfers you deserve, with top tier customer service. So, whether you’re trying to head to an event or get to the airport, Book us Today! Some of our services includes, but are not limited to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Where The Water Falls</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/go-where-the-water-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/go-where-the-water-falls/</guid>
      <description>Who ever said it was a bad idea to chase waterfalls? Home to many breathe taking sites, Grenada hosts so much untold beauties.
Journey through nature’s rich exhibits as we explore the natural tropical fountains. Indulge in nature’s gift to mankind, feast your eyes on her beauty, and enjoy the pure rhythms of the outdoors. Below is a list of Tropical Waterfalls for you to choose from, waiting to be explored by you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Life &amp; Luxury Taxi Services</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/night-life-luxury-taxi-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/night-life-luxury-taxi-services/</guid>
      <description>Get to and from your destination, in absolute comfort and luxury. Name your destination, your wish is our command. Some of the popular Night Life Hot spots includes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party On Board!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/party-on-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/party-on-board/</guid>
      <description>Grenada’s First Ever Party Bus with an on board fully stocked bar, fog machines, and party lights. Why not make the occasion a memorable one, by adding a touch of class. We have a variety of Party Bus event services for you to choose from, and not limited to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rum Tale</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/rum-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/rum-tale/</guid>
      <description>Entice your taste buds as you explore the wonders of the Flavours of Grenada’s Locally produced Rums. Journeying to the North of the island to River Antoine Rum Distillery, here you will experience up close and personal, the only authentic fully functional water driven mill on the island.
Experience rum making the old fashion way. The excitement continues as we venture over to the Westerhall Rum Distillery where you will tour the estate and view the ruins and museum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sip &amp; Tour</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/sip-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/sip-tour/</guid>
      <description>Our Signature Tour allows you to take any one of our amazing excursions and turn it into a private tour. Apart from all the wondrous tour highlights and adventures, our signature tour is all inclusive of food, snacks, our famous Grenadian Rum Punch and a well-stocked bar on board.
To top the fun off, exhilarating blended cocktails will also be served on board to tease your taste buds. You are free to wonder Grenada at your desired pace, free from any worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spice It Up Tour</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/spice-It-up-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/spice-It-up-tour/</guid>
      <description>Before rebranded as Pure Grenada, this tropical island was formerly known as ‘The Island of Spice.’ Grenada is widely known for its rich spices enjoyed worldwide.
This tour awards you the opportunity to stroll through the Laura Herb and Spice Garden, while enjoying an educational tour about the various trees, herbs and spices grown on the island. The fun continues as we venture over to the De La Grenade Factory, here you would enjoy the marvelous flavors of Grenada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Pic</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/take-a-pic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/take-a-pic/</guid>
      <description>Tired of the hustle and bustle of the city? Why not venture up to the north of the island to the boardwalk which extends into the tranquil waters of Levera Pond.
This wooden structure is surrounded by a flourishing mangrove reserve that is home to many wild species. Dangle your feet in the welcoming water of the pond as fishes jump to extend greetings, or update your Instagram with the scenic views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature Check</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/temperature-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/temperature-check/</guid>
      <description>Are you a lover of nature? Do you enjoy a good harsh or hike? Then we got just the right combination for you. Located in the middle of the rainforest reserves, sits one of the wonders of the islands, the seven sister’s waterfall.
After an approximate 15 minutes hike, enjoy the breath-taking scenery as the water cascades down the rocks, settling below to form inviting pools of water you can enjoy a refreshing swim at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tranquil Adventures</title>
      <link>http://example.org/service/tranquil-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/service/tranquil-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Journey up through the natural rain forest reserves. Feel the cool mist on your face as you inhale the pure air. Feast your eyes on the lush vegetation, and the tall pine trees with endemic fern in between. Indulge in the music sung by the birds, and enjoy the beautiful site of the mona monkeys swinging from branch to branch.
Stop at the highest motor point, “1910”, as you enjoy picturesque views of the south of the island.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
